biodigitalhuman.com 2013-10-06

# BioDigital Human

##### Personal Information Collected By BDS

##### Information You Provide to Us

We receive and store any information you enter on the Sites or through the Services or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the advertising and content you see, communicating with you about our products, and marketing our Services and those of our partners to you.

In order for you to use all of our features, you must register with BDS. We require your name, e-mail address and certain demographic information, such as location, during the registration process. We may also request optional demographic information and unique identifiers to provide you with a more personalized service. You may also provide personal information to us when you create public bookmarks or take quizzes on the Sites or using the Services. We store individual users' quiz results as well as aggregate results to compare our users' performance over time and with each other.

You may register for the Sites and the Services through a third-party service (e.g., Facebook or Twitter), in which case the third-party service through which you register will state the access we have to your personal information.

Further information may be required if you choose to purchase paid components of the Services, such as a physical address, order information, and billing information. BDS uses a third party partner, Braintree, for credit card processing, who may require and store your credit card and billing information. You can find [Braintree's privacy policy here](https://www.braintreepayments.com/privacy). We do not store your credit card information on the Sites but we may receive and store information from Braintree regarding a portion of your credit card number and other identifiers to identify your transaction through Braintree.

##### Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. BDS automatically receives and records "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, date and time of your visits to our Sites, your geographic location, BDS cookie information, and pages you request. BDS uses this traffic data to analyze trends and administer the Sites. Our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Sites and their components. This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often users use different parts of the Sites and Services. In addition, we may provide statistical collective user information, not information about you personally, to our partners so that they understand how often people use specific components of our Sites and Services.

##### E-mail Communications

If you contact us via e-mail through the Sites, we may retain a record of your contact information and any information you provide us in your message to respond to you. We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from BDS.

We may also send e-mails with news,promotions, service updates, or customer service communications. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please contact us at [support@biodigital.com](mailto:privacy@biodigital.com?subject=BioDigital%20Human%20Stop%20Emails&). If you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Sites and Services.

If your organization has an enterprise account with BDS, we will communicate with your designated contact person through e-mail or phone calls.

##### Information From Other Sources

To improve our Services, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Like the information you provide to us, we do not share this information with anyone except authorized third parties in connection with providing you with our Services.

##### Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Sites are visited and by how many people. BDS cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your name or e-mail address is.

Most browsers allow you to prevent the browser from accepting new cookies, to be notified when you receive a new cookie, or to disable cookies. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of some of BDS's features. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Sites. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

##### Sharing of Information by BDS

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control**

BDS may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. We will share customer information that is related to such transactions with those affiliated businesses. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use personal information for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction. BDS may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

  * **Agents**

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and services. Examples include billing, processing payments, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. Our agents subscribe to the same level of privacy protection as we do. Unless we tell you differently, BDS's agents do not have any right to use the personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

Financial and billing information collected through the Sites and Services is used solely to check the qualifications of prospective partners and customers and to bill for the Services. BDS may transmit this information to independent contractors who are bound to us by written confidentiality agreements. This billing information is not used by BDS for marketing or promotional purposes. BDS uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing who may store, retain, and use the information provided solely for the purpose of credit card processing.

  * **Promotional Offers**

We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses or provide our partners with the opportunity to notify users directly of promotions. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please e-mail us at [support@biodigital.com](mailto:privacy@biodigital.com?subject=BioDigital%20Human%20Stop%20Emails&)

  * **Information You Post**

When you post information on the Sites or through the Services, your username and certain profile information are visible to other users. BDS or other parties may use information posted by you, along with your profile information, in any medium now existing or developed in the future. BDS will use commercially reasonable efforts to attempt to notify you before using information posted by you along with your profile in other media.

  * **Business Transfers**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if BDS, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that BDS goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is reviewed and transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of BDS may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

  * **Protection of BDS and Others**

We may release personal information when we in our sole discretion believe in good faith that release is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of BDS, our employees, our users, or others.

  * **With Your Consent**

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties.

##### Information Security

Your BDS account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input. Only employees or agents who need personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. While BDS uses commercially reasonable means to secure your information, we do not guarantee that your personal information will not be improperly accessed, disclosed, or destroyed by breach of any of our safeguards.

##### Accessing Information

You are able to access, add to and update certain information about you. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may cancel your BDS Pro Account by following the process set forth on the Sites. Some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

##### Conditions of Use

Your use of the Sites and Services and any possible dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of New York state law.

##### International Visitors

For users outside the United States, please note that any data or personally identifiable information you enter into the Services or Sites will be transferred out of your country and into the United States. You consent to such transfer through your use of the Services and Sites. You also warrant that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country and into the United States.

##### Third Party Sites

The Sites and Services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Sites or Services. These other websites are not under BDS's control and BDS is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

BDS may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Sites.

##### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at BDS, please send us a detailed message to [support@biodigital.com](mailto:privacy@biodigital.com?subject=BioDigital%20Human%20Privacy%20Questions&) or to BIODIGITAL, INC. at 594 Broadway, Suite 606, New York, NY 10012. Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

© 2013 BIODIGITAL, INC. All rights reserved.   
Last Updated: September 2013
